Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
- College of Dentistry (RG 25), 1865-1984, April 2014-ongoing
  - New York College of Dentistry Annual Announcement and Catalogue, 1890-1891; cuid18328 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - New York College of Dentistry Annual Announcement and Catalogue, 1891-1892; cuid18329 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - New York College of Dentistry Annual Announcement and Catalogue, 1892-1893; cuid18330 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1896-1897; cuid18331 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1898-1899; cuid18332 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1907-1908; cuid18333 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1911-2023-03-27; cuid18334 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - New York College of Dentistry and Annex Announcement, 1914-1915; cuid18335 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1920-1921; cuid18336 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - The New York College of Dentistry Announcement, 1924-1925; cuid18337 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1925-1926; cuid18338 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - College of Dentistry, Program of Scientific Sessions and Alumni Meeting, December 1926; cuid18339 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1926-1927; cuid18340 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - College of Dentistry, Program of Lectures by Members of the Faculty, February 1927; cuid18341 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1927-1928; cuid18342 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1928-1929; cuid18343 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1929-1930; cuid18344 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1930-1931; cuid18345 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1932-1933; cuid18346 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - New York University, Washington Square College, College-Dental Curriculum Leading to the Bachelor of Arts and the Bachelor of Science, 1933; cuid18347 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1933-1934; cuid18348 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1934-1935; cuid18349 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - New York University Bulletin, College of Dentistry, 1935-1936; cuid18350 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Bulletins, 1899-1910 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins, 1903-1910 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1903-1910)
  - Bulletins, 1910-1915 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1910-1915)
  - Bulletins, 1910-1918 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins, 1915-1920 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1915-1920)
  - Bulletins, 1918-1925 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins, 1920-1925 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1920-1925)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1930 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins, 1930-1937 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1943 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1925-1943)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1939, 1942-1943, 1948-1957 (Box 81)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1949 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1936-1949)
  - Bulletins, 1937-1940 (Box 203)
  - New York College of Dentistry Bulletins, 1940-1943; cuid18192 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - New York College of Dentistry Announcements, 1942-1944, 1946, 1948-1951; cuid18193 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1951 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1948-1951)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1958 (Box 204)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1963 (Box 82)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1963 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1958-1963)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1967 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1967)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1971 (Box 83)
  - Bulletins, 1968-1973 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1968-1973)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1982 (Box 84)
  - Bulletins, 1973-1976 (Volume RG25 Bulletins - Bound 1973-1976)
  - Bulletins, 1982-1987 (Box 85)
  - Bulletins, 1987-2010 (Box 86)
  - Pre-doctoral curriculums, 1978-1984 (Box 87)
  - College of Dentistry Academic Bulletin, April 2014-May 2016
    Website for College of Dentistry Academic Bulletin for 2013-2014. The webpage redirects to the admissions and academic programs website for the Dentistry school.
  - College of Dentistry Admissions and Academic Programs, May 2015-June 2024
    Homepage for admissions and academic programs for College of Dentistry. Includes program information for the DDS program, Dental Hygiene programs, advanced education programs, programs for international dentists, certificate program in clinical research, and master's degree programs.
  - College of Dentistry DDS Course Inventory, May 2015-October 2019
    PDF that lists courses offered 2014-2015, 2015-2016, 2016-2017, 2017-2018 by the NYU School of Dentistry, including information about instructors, course types, number of credits, and course titles.
  - College of Dentistry Hygiene Curriculum, May 2015-March 2021
    PDF that lists courses offered by year for the BS in Dental Hygiene and AAS in Dental Hygiene in 2015.
  - College of Dentistry Dental Hygiene Programs, May 2015-June 2024
  - College of Dentistry Dental Hygiene Programs Courses and Curriculum, May 2015-February 2023
    Page that lists course descriptions and program requirements for the NYU School of Dentistry.
  - College of Dentistry Hygiene Degree Programs, May 2015-ongoing
    Website detailing the different degree programs in the Dental Hygiene programs track. It contains the Bachelor of Science tracks, Associate of Applied Science tracks, course descriptions, an FAQ, and degree requirements.
  - College of Dentistry MS in Biology, Oral Biology Track, May 2015-ongoing
    Web page for the Oral Biology track for the Master of Science program in Biology, hosted on the NYU School of Dentistry's site. Page includes information about degree requirements, faculty, and course syllabi, as well as links to other resources associated with the School of Dentistry.
  - College of Dentistry Academic Bulletin, May 2016-ongoing
    Academic bulletin for College of Dentistry. Includes program information for the DDS program, Dental Hygiene programs, advanced education programs, master's degree programs, certificate program in clinical research, programs for international dentists, and the Linhart Continuing Dental Education program.
  - College of Dentistry Education, June 2023-ongoing
  - College of Dentistry Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The College of Dentistry bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their graduate and certificate programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program and track.
  - College of Dentistry Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The College of Dentistry bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program and track.
- College of Dentistry - Post-Graduate Division (RG 25.1), 1926-2002
  - Bulletins, 1926-1932, 1934-1943, 1947-1956, 1957-1959 (Box 88)
  - Bulletins, 1959-1978, 1988-1990, 2002 (Box 89)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26), 1887-2015, April 2014-ongoing
  NYU Steinhardt offers undergraduate, master's, advanced certificate, and doctoral degree programs in applied psychology, the visual and performing arts and arts professions, education, health, and media. Undergraduate programs combine inquiry in the liberal arts and sciences, mastery of a specific field of study, global study, and applied learning, internship, and other fieldwork experiences. Graduate programs range from those that emphasize advanced research and scholarship to those that prepare students for advanced professional practice and leadership. Many graduate programs are interdisciplinary and include unique opportunities for global learning and research.
  - University of the City of New York, Graduate Division -- A Course of Lectures in Pedagogy Announcement to Teachers, 1887; cuid18194 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins of the School of Pedagogy, New York University, 1889-1900; cuid18351 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - University of the City of New York, School of Pedagogy, 1890-1891; cuid18352 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - University School of Pedagogy -- Announcements and Explanations, 1891; cuid18353 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - School of Pedagogy, New York University, New York City -- Announcement, 1897-1898; cuid18354 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- University School of Pedagogy, June 1901; cuid18355 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - New York University School of Pedagogy -- Announcement, September 1901; cuid18356 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- University School of Pedagogy, June 1902; cuid18357 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- University School of Pedagogy, May 1903; cuid18358 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- School of Pedagogy, June 1904; cuid18359 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - New York University School of Pedagogy -- Schedule of Lectures, 1911-1912; cuid18360 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - New York University Announcement -- Summer School, April 1914; cuid18361 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - New York University Bulletin -- School of Pedagogy, June 1914; cuid18362 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - New York University Announcement -- Summer School, February 1915; cuid18363 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - New York University School of Pedagogy -- Invoice from Registrar, circa 1911-1915; cuid18364 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Bulletins, 1900-1921 (Box 203)
  - Bulletins and related materials, 1914-1916, 1922-1942 (Box 91)
    Includes the Institute of Education.
  - Bulletins, 1921-1930 (Box 92)
  - Bulletins, 1923-1934 (Box 93)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1935 (Box 94)
  - Bulletins, 1934-1939 (Box 95)
  - Bulletins - Summer Session and Intersession, 1940-1946 (Box 201)
  - Bulletins, 1938-1941 (Box 96)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1946 (Box 97)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1949, 1952-1953 (Box 98)
    Includes Department of Dramatic Art (1952-1953).
  - Bulletins, 1946-1951 (Box 204)
  - Bulletins, 1951-1953 (Box 205)
  - Methods of Techniques in Social Recreation 180.298 syllabus, Spring 1954 (Box 91)
  - Bulletins, 1954-1955, 1959-1969 (Box 99)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1960 (Box 204)
  - Bulletins, 1969-1976 (Box 100)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1980 (Box 101)
  - Bulletins, 1980-1983 (Box 102)
  - Bulletins, 1983-1987 (Box 103)
  - Bulletins, 1987-1992 (Box 104)
  - Bulletins, 1992-1997 (Box 105)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2004 (Box 106)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2008 (Box 107)
  - Bulletins, 2008-2011 (Box 108)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins (PDFs), 2003-2014; cuid17991
  - Graduate Bulletins (PDFs), 2005-2015; cuid17992
  - Steinhardt School Bulletin, April 2014-October 2019
  - Steinhardt School Courses, May 2014-ongoing
    Website containing course listings for Steinhardt school-wide courses, including liberal arts CORE classes and interdisciplinary honors and seminars. The website also lists courses by departments; the departments include Administration, Leadership, and Technology; Applied Psychology; Art and Art Professions; Communicative Sciences and Disorders; Applied Statistics, Social Science, and Humanities; Media, Culture, and Communication; Music and Performing Arts Professions; Nutrition and Food Studies; Occupational Therapy; Physical Therapy; and Teaching and Learning.
  - Steinhardt School 2016-2018 Undergraduate Bulletin, October 2016-February 2019
    Steinhardt School undergraduate bulletin for the 126th and 127th sessions. The bulletin contains policies, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of the school and its departments and programs.
  - Steinhardt School Graduate Bulletin, November 2017-June 2019
    PDF of the Steinhardt graduate bulletin for 2017-2019.
  - Steinhardt School Undergraduate 2018-2020 Bulletin, February-June 2019
    PDF of the 2018-2020 undergraduate Bulletin for the Steinhardt School. Bulletin contains the policies, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of the school and its departments and programs.
  - Steinhardt School Graduate Bulletin 2017-2019, October 2019
    PDF of the Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Graduate Bulletin 2017-2019, which lists information about admissions, registration, departmental overviews, individual departments, and course listings.
  - Steinhardt School Bulletin 2018-2020, October 2019
    PDF of the Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Undergraduate Bulletin 2018-2020, which lists information about admissions, registration, departmental overviews, individual departments, and course listings.
  - Steinhardt School Bulletin, March 2020-ongoing
    PDFs of the undergraduate and graduate Steinhardt bulletins dating back to 2015.
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The Steinhardt bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their masters, certificate, PhD, and other doctoral programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each degree.
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The Steinhardt bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate majors and minors. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each degree.
- Stern School of Business (Undergraduate) (RG 27), 1900-2015
  - Bulletins, 1900-1913 (Box 205)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1906-1907, 1912-1916, 1920-1921, 1923-1924, 1927-1935 (Box 109)
    Includes copies of addresses delivered under the Don R. Mellett Memorial Fund for the Department of Journalism (1931-1935).
  - Bulletins, 1913-1921 (Box 205)
  - Bulletins, 1921-1926 (Box 205)
  - Bulletins, 1926-1933 (Box 206)
  - Programs, 1928-1929 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1929-1930 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1930-1931 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1931-1932 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1932-1933 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1933-1934 (Box 207)
  - Bulletins, 1933-1941 (Box 206)
  - Programs, 1934-1935 (Box 207)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1934-1963 (Box 110)
  - Programs, 1935-1936 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1936-1937 (Box 207)
  - Programs, 1937-1938 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1938-1939 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1939-1940 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1940-1941 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1941-1942 (Box 209)
  - Bulletins, 1941-1949 (Box 206)
  - Programs, 1942-1943 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1943-1944 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1944-1945 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1945-1946 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1946-1947 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1947-1948 (Box 209)
  - Programs, 1948-1949 (Box 209)
  - Bulletins, 1949-1955 (Box 206)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1962 (Box 207)
  - Bulletins, 1962-1963 (Box 207)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1963-1972 (Box 111)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1972-1985 (Box 112)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1984-1998 (Box 113)
  - Bulletins and Programs, 1998-2010 (Box 114)
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2013-2015; cuid17993
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Undergraduate Bulletin, February 2024-ongoing
    The Stern bulletin provides an overview of the policies, requirements, accreditation, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of Stern's undergraduate program. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program and interdisciplinary minors.
- Stern School of Business (Graduate) (RG 28), 1916-2016
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Bulletins, 1916-1917, 1919-1931 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1918-1921, 1940-1941, 1945-1946, 1950-1951, 1952-1953, 1954-1955, 1959-1979 (Box 115)
    Includes Summer School bulletins (1959-1963).
  - Bulletins, 1931-1944 (Box 208)
  - Bulletins, 1945-1953 (Box 208)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1963 (Box 208)
  - Bulletins, 1963-1971 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1963-1971)
  - Bulletins, 1972-1978 (Volume RG28 Bulletins - Bound 1972-1978)
  - Bulletins, 1979-1985 (Box 116)
  - Bulletins, 1985-1991 (Box 117)
  - Bulletins, 1993-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 118)
  - Bulletins, 2002-2005, 2008-2010 (Box 119)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2000-2016; cuid17994
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The Stern bulletin provides an overview of the policies, requirements, accreditation, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of Stern's certificate, doctoral, dual degree, executive, and masters programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program.
- School of Commerce, Accounts and Finance - Wall Street Division (RG 28.9), 1915-1940
  - Bulletins, 1915-1916, 1917-1919, 1920-1940 (Box 120)
- Faculty of Business Administration (FBA) / School of Business, 1980-1984
  - Computer Applications and Information Systems Bulletins, 1980-1984 (Box Shared University Archives 149, Folder 4)
- School of Retailing/Institute of Retail Management (RG 30), 1922-1978
  - Bulletins, 1922-1948 (Box 208)
  - Bulletins, 1948-1963 (Box 209)
  - Bulletins, 1919, 1922-1923, 1925-1927, 1928-1933, 1934-1941, 1955-1958 (Box 121)
    Includes proposed course of study for Training School for Teachers of Retail Selling (1919).
  - Bulletins, 1959-1978 (Box 122)
- School of Architecture and Allied Arts (RG 31), 1926-1941
  - Fine Arts and Architecture Bulletins, 1926-1939; cuid18195 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins, 1929-1935, 1940-1941 (Box 123)
- School of Professional Studies (RG 32), 1903-ongoing
  Includes Extramural Divisions, Extension Divisions, and Division of General Education.
  - Bulletins, 1903-1904, 1916-1941 (Box 124)
  - Bulletins, 1934-1941, 1952-1957 (Box 125)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1950 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1950)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1951 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1951)
  - Bulletins - Course for Adults, 1952 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1952)
  - Bulletins, 1958-1959, 1961-1965, 1967-1970 (Box 126)
  - Bulletins - Courses Open to the Public, 1965-1967 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1965-1967)
  - Bulletins - Courses Open to the Public, 1967-1969 (Volume RG32 Bulletins - Bound 1967-1969)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1973 (Box 127)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 128)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1979 (Box 129)
  - Bulletins, 1979-1980 (Box 130)
  - Bulletins, 1981-1982 (Box 131)
  - Bulletins, 1983-1984 (Box 132)
  - Bulletins, 1984-1986 (Box 133)
  - Bulletins, 1986-1988 (Box 134)
  - Bulletins, 1988-1990 (Box 135)
  - Diploma in Bank Lending, Concentration in Credit Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 135)
  - Bulletins, 1990-1992, 1994-1996 (Box 136)
  - Bulletins, 1992-1995 (Box 137)
  - Bulletins, 1996-1998 (Box 138)
  - Bulletins, 1998-1999 (Box 139)
  - Bulletins, 1999-2000 (Box 140)
  - Bulletins, 2000-2001 (Box 141)
  - Bulletins, 2002-2003 (Box 142)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2004 (Box 143)
  - Bulletins, 2005-2007 (Box 144)
  - Bulletins, 2007-2009 (Box 145)
  - Bulletins, 2009-2010, 2012, 2014 (Box 146)
  - Bulletins, 2015 (Box 147)
  - School of Continuing and Professional Studies Bulletin, April 2014-August 2018
    This website contains the SCPS bulletins from Summer 2014 to Fall 2015. Program areas covered include Applied Politics, Business, Creative Cities and Economic Development, Global Affairs, Health and Care Programs, Hospitality and Tourism, Languages and Humanities, Media Industry Studies and Design, Philanthropy and Fundraising, Real Estate, and Sports Management, Media, and Business.
  - School of Professional Studies Degree Programs, October 2018-February 2019
    Information on the undergraduate, graduate, and online programs at the School of Professional Studies.
  - School of Professional Studies Career Advancement Courses, October 2018-ongoing
    A website detailing course offerings from the School of Professional Studies.
  - School of Professional Studies Divisions and Departments, August 2019-ongoing
    Website listing the divisions and departments in NYUSPS. NYUSPS is made up the Center for Applied Liberal Arts, Center for Global Affairs, Center for Publishing, Division of Applied Undergraduate Studies, Division of Programs in Business, English Language Institute, Jonathan M. Tisch Center of Hospitality, Preston Robert Tisch Institute for Global Sport, and the Schack Institute of Real Estate. Each division page is divided into programs, which consists of degree details containing course descriptions for required and elective courses for each degree.
  - School of Professional Studies Academics, August 2019-ongoing
    Landing page detailing programs and degrees associated with NYUSPS.
  - School of Professional Studies Master's Degrees, August 2019-ongoing
    This page details master's degree programs offered by the NYU School of Professional Studies, with links to individual programs where users can find information about admissions requirements, course listings and degree requirements, financing information, and general structural information about the program. Programs include an MS in Construction Management, MS in Event Management, MS in Global Affairs, MS in Global Security Conflict and Cyber Crime (STEM), MS in Global Sport, MS in Hospitality Industry Studies, MS in Human Capital Analytics and Technology (STEM), MS in Human Resource Management and Development, MS in Integrated Marketing, MS in Management and Systems (STEM), MS in Professional Writing, MS in Project Management (STEM), MS in Public Relations and Corporate Communication, MS in Publishing, MS in Real Estate, MS in Real Estate Development, MS in Sports Business, MS in Tourism Management, and MS in Translation.
  - School of Professional Studies Bachelor's Degrees, August 2019-ongoing
    This page contains information about the bachelor's degree programs offered by NYU's School of Professional Studies, and features navigable links to pages describing each degree program individually, including admissions requirements, coursework and degree requirements, and financing options. Programs include BS in Hotel and Tourism Management, BS in Real Estate, BS in Sports Management, BS in Applied Data Analytics and Visualization, BA in Applied General Studies, BS in Digital Communications and Media, BA in Social Sciences, BS in Leadership and Management Studies, BS in Information Systems Management, BS in Real Estate, BA in Humanities, BS in Marketing Analytics, and BS in Healthcare Management.
  - School of Professional Studies Associate Degrees, August 2019-ongoing
    Overview of associate degrees programs at the School of Professional Studies, including descriptions and degree requirements for individual programs, as well as admissions criteria and financing information. Associate degrees include an AAS in Business, AA in Liberal Arts, AAS in Health Administration, and AAS in Information Systems Management.
  - School of Professional Studies Online Degree Programs, August 2019-ongoing
    This page details the online degree programs offered by NYU's School of Professional Studies. There are links to individual degree program pages that include information about those programs' degree requirements, courses, admissions criteria, career outlooks, and financing options. Online programs include an MS in Global Sport, MS in Human Capital Analytics and Technology (STEM), MS in Human Resource Management and Development, MS in Professional Writing, MS in Project Management (STEM), MS in Translation, BA in Social Sciences, and a BS in Leadership and Management Studies.